<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Compliance Week eBooks Schedule</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>eBooks - Q2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Compliance Week eBook Topics - Q2 2018</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Contact.FirstName},

Compliance Week has identified a number of eBooks that we&apos;d like to release in Q2, I would like to approach your firm with sponsorship options.

As an eBook sponsor, your firm would be able to contribute a white paper and full page advertisement. Your logo would appear on the front cover and in all promotional materials, and your firm description would appear on the second page. You would also receive all registration information for marketing.  eBooks are a great opportunity for both lead generation and branding. The eBook topics we are ready to release include:


eBook: Keeping up with Cryptocurrencies and Blockchain
Technological advances like virtual currencies and blockchain are creating both new risks and opportunities for companies. Cryptocurrencies, for example, mean that companies must evolve their money laundering controls and sanctions restrictions. They’re also creating a new breed of hackers, increasing a company’s cyber threats. And in the audit world, blockchain is evolving rapidly from enigma to imperative in financial reporting circles. To stay in step with audit technology, companies need to start thinking hard about their own technological capabilities to stand up to the audit process.

eBook: Preventing Corruption and Legal Risk in Sports
There’s no shortage of corruption investigations in sports these days. From bribery allegations surrounding FIFA, doping allegations surrounding the International Association of Athletics Federations (IAAF), growing corruption allegations in college sports, and more, now is as good of a time as any for compliance officers at companies to ensure their corporate sponsorship practices and do not create legal risk, and further that college and university compliance departments are doing everything they can to avoid becoming the target of the next big corruption investigation in college sports. In this eBook, compliance and ethics officers will learn how to ensure that their corporate media departments and the company’s code of conduct are in sync. This ebook also includes a conversation with International Centre for Sport Security CEO Michael Hershman’s, who shares his views on bringing honesty and transparency to the world of professional sports. Finally, this eBook will take a look at a new policy adopted by the Olympics, starting with the 2024 Summer Games in Paris, calling on host cities to abide by certain anti-corruption and human rights principles meant to clean up the world of global sports.

eBook: An Industry Perspective of GDPR Compliance
Data privacy is a hot topic and high on the priority list for many global companies today. This eBook will focus on data privacy efforts from the trenches, leading up to the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation. First, this eBook will explore how forward-thinking companies are adjusting their compliance policies and procedures in response to the GDPR. This eBook will also take a look at the hard lessons of Facebook, and what it could mean for GDPR-like privacy controls in the United States.  Other compliance challenges of GDPR will also be explored in this eBook. We’ll also explore what innovative and technological advances companies are making to address the challenge.

eBook: How Technology is Transforming the Financial Services Industry
Technology is transforming the financial services industry in remarkable and significant ways. New intelligence is calling on audit leaders to embrace their new normal—that nothing is normal—and innovate with technology to face it. Financial institutions are also starting to think creatively—voluntarily banding together to strengthen their cyber-security defenses and provide additional protections for consumer account information. Evolving technology and cyber-threats are also transforming the way board members and senior executives must think about cyber threats and ways to protect the business. This eBook will explore all these developments and much more.

eBook: Ridding Toxins out of Corporate Culture
Corporate governance failures, sexual harassment allegations, ethical and integrity lapses—they all begin and end with corporate culture. This eBook will take a look at real-life lessons learned from culture mishaps, and what crucial role ethics and compliance officers play. This eBook will also explore how to enhance your company’s sexual harassment policies and procedures; creative ways to foster an ethical culture; and metrics to gauge their effectiveness.

eBook: Answering the Call of Today’s Investor Demands
Dramatic evolution is underway in terms of how shareholders influence the strategy and social responsibility of the companies in which they invest.  On the global front, a recent report finds that the lure of cross-border investors is doing as much to demand corporate best practices as government rule regimes. And in the United States, early pay ratio filings show a disclosure demand in progress. Moreover, SEC Chairman Jay Clayton has floated the idea of mandatory shareholder arbitration, raising issues about agency enforcement and investor protection. These are just a few of the shareholder issues companies must contend with today.  This eBook will also explore what lessons ethics and compliance officers can learn from Novartis, which faced a firestorm of criticism from shareholders at its last annual meeting, as well as from Broadcom and its hostile takeover of Qualcomm.

eBook: A Global Look at Anti-Corruption Laws
Anti-corruption developments continue at full speed ahead around the globe—from the newly released FCPA Corporate Enforcement Policy to a newly implemented ban on facilitation payments in Canada, to global corruption investigations in countries around the world entangling major international companies, it’s hard for risk, compliance, and audit executives to keep up with it all. This eBook will cover what’s been happening in the world of anti-bribery and anti-corruption, and what due diligence, risk management, compliance lessons can be learned along the way.

eBook: Updates in the World of Internal Audit
Internal audit plans for 2018 will reflect more consideration of corporate culture and the risks it might pose to the company’s success. This eBook explores all those issues—from technological solutions to culture to accounting requirements and so much more.

eBook: Artificial Intelligence
Corporate compliance is an increasingly technology-driven discipline, and nowhere do we see that more than to the extent that artificial intelligence is helping to streamline, improve, and evolve compliance efforts. For many compliance officers, “artificial intelligence” is a buzzword often heard, but not always understood. But for those overseeing operations that handle large data sets and volumes of transactions, AI is already a reality. Using powerful programs that can oversee enormous amounts of data and/or transactions in the blink of an eye, computerized systems can provide a first pass for flagging questionable transactions, potential compliance violations, potential legal issues, and more. But where the AI comes in is with systems that can take disparate points of data and make its own correlations between them – so that humans don’t have to – thereby making that first level of compliance monitoring far more deep and efficient, enabling human compliance experts to shift their own efforts from transnational monitoring to more high-level, strategic risk management. This e-Book looks at some of the most recent developments as AI evolves as a technology, and as part of today’s compliance discipline.

eBook: Navigating the Worldwide Web of Trade Sanctions Laws
For years, managing sanctions risk has centered on the bright line marking where an organization can and cannot do business around the world. But as the compliance function has evolved into a strategic advisory role, so too has sanctions risk itself, involving pre-emptive regulatory intervention on mergers and acquisitions, politically exposed persons, and more. In this e-Book, produced by Compliance Week in partnership with Amber Road, companies will learn how to navigate the complex world of sanctions risk with an eye toward not just abiding by the law, but to helping inform better enterprise-wide business decision-making in the realms of product development, international expansion, and more.  Specifically, this eBook will explore sanctions in Iran, Russian, and Sudan, and how compliance professionals can manage these risks while still engaging in legitimate trade. This eBook will also explore the United Kingdom’s sanctions regulations, and what it means for companies in the wake of Brexit.

eBook: Data Privacy
Gathering, processing and utilizing data from customers, clients and contacts is a hallmark of modern business. But as organizations harness the power of all of this information, they must face new responsibilities and risks, especially those regarding a need to properly safeguard this data. With strong new rules such as New York’s Cybersecurity Regulation and the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation in play, compliance officers must ensure that their organizations are respecting the privacy of their data subjects. That means making sure bad actors don’t gain access to the information, respecting subjects’ requests to be purged from databases, and more. This new eBook from Compliance Week will discuss how compliance officers are keeping up with proliferating rules and developing the best practices to keep the confidence of their stakeholders on what is an increasingly difficult challenge to manage.

Each eBook will be published online and will be released via email to Compliance Week’s entire active online database of 72,000 corporate financial, legal, audit, risk &amp; compliance executives at global public companies. We will also promote the eBook on our website homepage for three weeks and we’ll archive the eBook in our online library for one year. The online promotion will generate a MINIMUM of 300 registrations with all registration information shared with the sponsor.  The cost for exclusive sponsorship of an eBook is $15,000 and benefits include:

Full page advertisement in the eBook
White paper in the eBook (content prepared and formatted by the sponsor)
Logo on all promotional materials including front cover
Company description on page two of the eBook
Ability to cross promote the eBook to own clients
Leads from all promotion (minimum 300 leads guaranteed)

Please let me know if you have questions or would like to see a sample eBook. Thanks for your consideration.



-Doug



----------------------------------
Doug Juenemann
Advertising &amp; Events
Compliance Week
djuenemann@complianceweek.com
(617) 570 8610</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
